本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
你准备好面对终极挑战了吗
Are you ready for the ultimate challenge?
时刻准备着
I'm always ready!
那你知道这意味着什么吧
Then you know what this means!
糖浆比赛
Syrup race!
-来吧  糖浆爵士  -来吧  骑警先生
- Go, sir syrup! - Go, mountie man!
-来啊来啊  -快了  快了
- Go go! Go go! - Almost... Almost...
耶
Yes!
我赢了
I won!
噢  不是吧
Ho ho, no way!
梅宝  你看这个
Hey, Mabel, check this out.
真人大小的仓鼠球
Human-sized hamster balls?
我就是真人大小的
I'm human-sized!
不不  梅宝  我是指这个
No, no, Mabel. This.
我们每天都能看到比这个更古怪的东西
We see weirder stuff than that every day.
怪物拍照比赛
赢得1000元
我们没有给那些小矮人拍下照片  对吧
We didn't get any photos of those gnomes, did we?
没有  只有回忆  跟这撮胡子
Nope, just memories. And this beard hair.
你留着它干嘛
Why did you save that?
早上好  蠢蛋们
Uhh! Good morning, knuckleheads.
你们知道今天是什么日子吗
You two know what day it is?
呃  周年纪念日吗
Um... Happy anniversary?
好运日吗
Mazel tov!
是家庭欢乐日啊  天才们
It's family fun day, genius!
今天我们不工作  然后尝试干点儿  你懂的
We're cuttin' off work and havin' one of those, ya know,
就是联络感情的事儿
Bonding-type deals.
斯坦叔公  这次会像
Grunkle Stan, is this gonna
上次的家庭欢乐日那样吗
be anything like our last family bonding day?
你管这人叫富兰克林  他看起来像个女的
You call that Ben Franklin? He looks like a woman!
糟了
Uh-oh!
哎  县监狱太寒冷了
Ohh! The county jail was so cold.
好吧  或许我不是最佳夏日监护人
All right, maybe I haven't been the best summer caretaker.
但我发誓  今天我们会享受到真正的家庭乐趣
But I swear, today we're gonna have some real family fun.
现在  谁想戴上眼罩然后跟我上车啊
Now, who wants to put on some blindfolds and get into my car?
-耶  -耶
- Yay! - Yay!
等一下  什么
Wait. What?
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
翻译： Sarina
校订： WaitinZ
■
后期： WaitinZ  leland
怪诞小镇  第一季第二集
Gravity Falls  S01E02  The Legend of Gobblewonker
戴眼罩从来不会遇上什么好事
Blindfolds never lead to anything good.
哇  我感觉我的其他感官功能都加强了
Wow. I feel like all my other senses are heightened.
我能用手指看东西
I can see with my fingers.
斯坦叔公  你也带眼罩了吗
Grunkle Stan, are you wearing a blindfold?
哈哈  没有  但我的白内障跟戴了眼罩差不多
Ha ha! Nah, but with these cataracts, I might as well be.
那是什么  啄木鸟吗
What is that, a woodpecker?
好了好了  拿下眼罩
Okay, okay, open 'em up.
看啊  现在是钓鱼季节
Ta-da! It's fishin' season!
-钓鱼  -你想玩什么  老家伙
- Fishing? - What are you playing at, old man?
你们会喜欢钓鱼的  整个小镇的人都到这里来了
You're gonna love it! The whole town's out here!
来吧  多心的鱼儿  快到锅里来
Here, fishy-fishies! Get into the pan.
说茄子
Say "Cheese."
呃  这样行吗
Uh, is this good?
不行
No!!!
我来告诉你们真正的男子汉是怎么钓鱼的
I'll show you how a real man fishes!
-好啊  好啊  -好啊  好啊
- Dead! Dead! - Dead! Dead!
打得好  打得好
Get him! Get him!
那才是像样的感情联络嘛
That's some quality family bonding!
斯坦叔公  为什么你突然想跟我们联络感情
Uncle Stan, why do you want to bond with us all of a sudden?
拜托  这将会非常有趣的
Come on, this is gonna be great!
我从来没有过钓鱼伙伴
I've never had fishin' buddies before.
共济会的那些家伙不肯跟我来
The guys from the lodge won't go with me.
他们既不喜欢或  也不信任我
They don't like or trust me.
我觉得他真的想跟我们一起钓鱼呢
I think he actually wants to fish with us.
我知道要怎么让你们两小鬼高兴起来
Hey, I know what'll cheer you sad sacks up.
派恩斯家钓鱼帽
Pines family fishin' hats.
那是手缝的  知道吗
That's hand-stitching, ya know.
今天将会是只有你们俩  跟我
It's just gonna be you, me,
还有这两顶古怪帽子  在船上一起度过的美妙十小时
and those goofy hats on a boat for ten hours!
十小时
Ten hours?!
我带了笑话书
I brought the joke book.
不  不
No. No!
肯定有什么办法能逃走
There has to be a way out of this.
我看见它了
I seen it!
我又看见它了
I seen it again!
重力泉的湖怪
The Gravity Falls gobblewonker!
快赶在它窜走前看一眼
Come quick before he scrapdoodles away!
啊  他在跳开心舞
Aw. He's doing a happy jig.
不  这是死亡之舞
No!!! It's a jig of grave danger!
我跟你说过不要骚扰我的客人
Now, what did I tell you about scaring my customers?
这是给你的终极警告  老爸
This is your last warning, dad.
但是我这次找到证据了
But I got proof this time, by gummity!
看啊
Behold!
是那只湖怪干的好事
It's gobbledywonker what done did it!
它的脖子就像长颈鹿那么长
It had a long neck like a gee-raffe,
-而且它的皮肤满布皱纹  就像这位先生这样  -什么
- and wrinkly skin like... like this gentleman right here. - Huh?
它把我的船撕成了木块
It chopped my boat up to smitheroons!
而且它向水桶岛游去了
It shim-shammed over to Scuttlebutt Island!
你们一定要相信我
Ya gotta believe me!!!
各部门注意
Attention, all units.
我们遇到了一个发疯的老人
We got ourselves a crazy old man.
哎  驴唾沫  波兰班卓
Aw, donkey spittle! Banjo Polish...
哎  这是常有的事
Well, that happened.
现在我们要解开绳索  向湖中心出发
Now, let's untie this boat and get out on that lake!
梅宝  你听到那个老人说什么了吗
Mabel, did you hear what that old dude said?
哎  驴唾液
"Aw, donkey spittle!"
是另一句话  那个怪物的事情
The other thing... about the monster.
如果我们能拍到湖怪的照片
If we can snag a photo of it,
我们就可以平分奖品
we could split the prize fifty-fifty.
那是两个五十耶
That's two fifties!
想象一下如果你有五百块钱会怎么用
Imagine what you could do with five hundred dollars!
嚣张不起来了吧
Not so high and mighty anymore.
你好啊  帅哥们
Hey, boys.
只可远观不可亵玩哦
You can look... But you can't touch.
吱吱吱吱
Squeak! Squeak! Squeak! Squeak!
吱吱
Squeak squeak...
太赞了
Awesome!
梅宝  梅宝
Mabel. Mabel?
迪普  我百分百同意这事儿
Dipper, I am one million percent onboard with this!
斯坦叔公  计划有变
Grunkle Stan! Change of plans!
我们要坐船去水桶岛
We're taking that boat to Scuttlebutt Island,
而且我们要找湖怪
and we are gonna find that gobblewonker.
-猎湖怪  -猎湖怪
- Monster Hunt! - Monster Hunt!
-湖怪  -猎湖怪
- Monster... - Monster Hunt!
湖怪  呃
Monster... eh...
我还是走吧
I'll go.
你们是说想去猎湖怪吗
You dudes say something about a monster Hunt?
-苏斯  -你好啊  小家伙
- Zeus! - What's up, hambone?
-噼里啪啦  -嘭  爆炸
- Kapoosh! - Pow! Explode!
伙计们  你们可以乘我的船去猎湖怪
Dude, you could totally use my boat for your Hunt.
船上有方向盘  椅子  还有该有的设备
It's got a steering wheel, chairs... normal boat stuff.
好了好了  让我好好想想
All right, let's think this through.
你们俩可以选择参加浪费时间的猎湖怪冒险
You kids could go waste your time on some epic monster-finding adventure,
或者跟你们伟大的
or you could spend the day
斯坦叔公学习绑绳结跟串虫子
learning how to tie knots and skewer worms with your great uncle Stan!
怎么样
So, whaddya say?
我们作了正确的抉择
We made the right choice!
忘恩无义的家伙  谁需要他们啊
Ingrates! Ah, who needs 'em?
我有一盒奇怪的鱼饵作伴呢
I got a whole box of creepy fishin' lures to keep me company.
起锚
Hoist the anchor!
升旗
Raise the flag!
我们要找到湖怪
We're gonna find that gobblewonker!
我们要赢得照相比赛
We're gonna win that photo contest!
你们两带防晒油了吗
Do any of you dudes have sunscreen?
我们要  要去拿防晒油
We're gonna... Go get sunscreen!
耶
Yay!
好吧  如果我们想赢比赛
All right, if we want to win this contest,
我们就得把事情做对
we've gotta do it right.
大家想想  对于湖怪猎人来说最重要的问题是什么
Think. What the #1 problem with most monster hunts?
你只是个配角
You're a side character and
而且你在电影出场五分钟后就挂了
you die in the first five minutes of the movie.
伙计  我是个配角吗
Dude, am I a side character?
你们考虑这些问题吗
Do you ever think about stuff like that?
不不不  是相机问题
No, no, no... camera trouble.
例如说大脚兽出现了  苏斯  你扮大脚兽
Say bigfoot shows up. Zeus, be bigfoot.
他就在那里  大脚兽
There he is! Bigfoot!
糟了  没有相机
Uh-oh! No camera!
哦  等一下  相机在这里
Oh, wait! Here's one!
哎  没有胶卷
Aw, no film!
你懂我的意思吗
You see what I'm doing here?
-嗯  -这家伙说得有道理
- Uh-huh. - Dude's got a point.
所以我买了十七部一次性照相机
That's why I bought seventeen disposable cameras.
两部藏在我的脚踝边  三部在我的夹克里
Two on my ankle, three in my jacket,
你们每人四部  另外三部在这个包里面
four for each of you, three extras in this bag,
还有一部在我的帽子下面
and one under my hat.
我们肯定不会错过拍照机会
There's no way we're gonna Miss this.
好了  伙计们  开始测试相机
Okay, everybody, let's test our cameras out.
哎  伙计
Ahh! Dude!
看见了吗  这就是为什么你们需要后备相机
You see? This is exactly why you need backup cameras.
我们还有十六部
We still have sixteen.
哎  笨鸟
Ahh! Bird!
十五部  好了  伙计们  我重申一遍  不要弄丢相机
Fifteen. Okay, guys, I repeat, don't lose your cameras.
-什么  丢掉相机  -别
- Wait. Lose the cameras? - Don't!
伙计  我刚刚扔掉了两部
Dude, I just threw two away.
十三部
Thirteen!
好了  我们还有十三部相机
All right, we still have thirteen camera...
十二部  我们有十二部相机
Twelve. We have twelve cameras.
计划到底是什么  向湖里扔更多相机还是什么
So what's the plan? Throw more cameras overboard or what?
不  不  好了
No! No. Okay.
你当哨兵  苏斯开船
You'll be lookout, Zeus can work the steering wheel,
-而我就是船长  -什么
- and I'll be captain. - What?!
为什么你可以当船长
Why do you get to be captain?
梅宝当船长怎么样
What about Mabel, huh?
梅宝  梅宝
Ma-bel! Ma-bel!
我不确定这是个好主意
I'm not sure that's a good idea.
副船长怎么样
What about co-captain?
根本没有副船长这回事
There's no such thing as co-captain.
哦  遭了
Ohh. Whoops!
好了  行  你可以当副船长
Okay, fine! You can be co-captain!
我可以当副船长助理吗
Can I be associate co-captain?
作为副船长  我批准你的请求
As co-captain, I authorize that request.
作为首席船长  我们的首要任务是
Well, as first co-captain, our #1 order of business
用这东西把海怪引出来
is to lure the monster out with this.
允许我品尝一下么
Permission to taste some?
-许可  -副船长许可
- Granted. - Permission co-granted.
副船长助手也许可
Permission associate go-granted.
老天  我真不知道在期望什么味道
Dude, I don't know what I expected that to taste like.
叛徒  我会找到其他钓鱼伙伴的
Traitors! I'll find my own fishin' buddies.
那就是我的新伙伴
There's my new pals!
现在只有我们两个人  罗莎娜
Now that we're alone, Rosanna,
我心中一直有个重要的问题想问你
there's a burning question which my heart longs to ask of you.
-噢  雷吉诺德  -嗨
- Oh, Reginald! - Hey!
想听个笑话吗
Wanna hear a joke?
开始啦
Here goes.
我的前妻依然想念我
My ex-wife still misses me,
但是她的目标是过得更好
but her aim is gettin' better!
她的目标是过得更好
Her aim is gettin' better!
你懂吗  这笑话好笑是因为婚姻糟透了
Ya see, it's... it's funny because marriage is terrible.
干嘛
What?!
嗨  事情进展怎样
Hey, how's it going?
非常好
It's going awesome.
梅宝  别玩那东西
Mabel, leave that thing alone.
啊  我不介意
Aw, I don't mind none!
喂  快看  我在喝水
Hey, look, I'm drinking water!
一闪一闪亮
Grinkle, grinkle, little...
你不是应该要t望吗
Aren't you supposed to be doing lookout?
小心
Look out!
但是放心  我警惕着呢
But seriously, I'm on it.
看见了吗  我们到了
See? We're here.
我是个t望天才
I'm a lookout genius!
仓鼠球  我们来了
Hamster ball, here we come!
伙计  你看这个
Dude, check it out.
屁屁岛
Butt island.
苏斯  你这坏家伙
Zeus, you rapscallion!
喂  你干嘛不笑
Hey, why aren't you laughing?
你害怕了吗
Are you scared?
哦  才怪  我才不
Yeah, right. I'm not...
-你就是害怕  -喂
- Yeah, you are! - Hey...
别玩了
Quit it...
别别  梅宝  啊
stop, Mabel! Uhh! Uhh!
你们听到了吗
Dude, did you guys hear that?
那是什么  是从你肚子里发出来的吗
What was that? Was it your stomach?
不是  我的肚子通常发出像鲸鱼叫的声音
No, my stomach normally sounds like whale noises.
哇  太壮丽了
Wow! So majestic!
我们的灯
Our lantern!
啊  我什么都看不见了
Ahh! I can't see anything!
伙计  我不知道  但是这可能并不值得
Dude, I don't know, man, maybe this isn't worth it.
不值得  伙计  想象下如果我们
Not worth it? Guys, imagine what would happen
拍到照片了会怎样
if we got that picture!
今晚  我们请来了拍出难以捉摸的湖怪照片的
Tonight, we're here with adventure-seeker Dipper Pines
伟大冒险家迪普・派恩斯
who bravely photographed the elusive gobblewonker.
告诉我  迪普  你的成功秘诀是什么
Tell me, Dipper, what's the secret to your success?
那个  就是勇往直前
Well, I run away from nothing...
当然除了我烦人的斯坦叔公以外
Nothing except for when I ran away from my annoying Grunkle Stan
我丢下他去找湖怪
who I ditched in order to pursue that lake monster.
你做得真对  他看起来真像个讨厌鬼
How right you were to do so. He looked like a real piece of work.
我不常干这事  但我觉得有必要给你颁块金牌
I don't often do this, but I feel the need to give you an award.
查理
Charlie!
为什么你不采访我
Why won't you interview me?!
-我要参加  -我也是
- I'm in! - Me too!
好了  伙计  我就来
All right, dudes, I'm comin!
我的名字叫梅宝  它跟桌子押韵  也跟格莱贝尔押韵
My name is mable, it rhymes with "Table" It also rhymes with "Glable"
-也跟斯美宝押韵  -伙计  我们应该把这些写下来
- It also rhymes with "Schmable" - Dude, we should be writing this down.
伙计们  你们听到了吗
Guys! Guys, guys. You hear something?
我们到了  我们到了
This is it. This is it!
-啊  -这真是太棒了
- Uh. Uh... - This is cooooool!
大家准备好相机
Everyone... Get your cameras ready.
准备好了吗  跑
Ready? Go!
我爱欢蹦乱跳
这值得我们拥抱一下
但  但刚刚那是什么声音
But... but what was that noise, then?
我听到了怪物的声音
I heard a monster noise.
太赞了  河狸玩电锯
Sweet! Beaver with a chainsaw!
或许那个老家伙确实是个疯子
Maybe that old guy was crazy after all.
他确实用了窜走这词儿
He did use the word "Scrapdoodle."
听着  当你绑线的时候
Look, when you're threading the line...
很多人不懂这个
a lot of people don't know this...
但是你应该用桶结
but you want to use a barrel knot.
这是钓鱼伙伴间的秘密
That's a secret from one fishin' buddy to another.
我  呃  你到底是谁
I, uh... who are you, exactly?
叫我斯坦叔公就行
Just call me your Grunkle Stan!
先生  先生
Sir... sir!
你为什么跟我们的儿子说话
Why are you talking to our son?!
如果你不离开  我就报警了
If you don't leave right now, I'm calling the police!
哈哈  你懂吗  这事情其实是
Ha ha! Ya see, the thing about that is...
去烦你自己的孩子去
Go bother your own kids!
噢  对  做的好  好  很好  很好
Ooh, yeah, work it, work it! Nice! Nice!
再做一遍这个姿势  对  我喜欢这姿势
Give me another one of those. Yeah, I like that one.
我们要怎么跟斯坦叔公解释
What are we gonna say to Grunkle Stan?
我们为了无中生有的事甩了他
We ditched him over nothing.
伙计们  你们感觉到了吗
Hey. Guys, do you feel that?
就是它了
This is it!
快点  这是我们仅有的机会
Come on, this is our chance!
你们怎么了
What's wrong with you guys?
-迪普  -天哪
- Dipper... - Dude...
这事情没那么难办  好吗
It's not that hard, all right?
你只需要定位  然后拍照  就像这样
All you gotta do is point and shoot. Like this.
快跑
Run!
回到船上  快跑
Get back to the boat! Hurry!!!
我的照片
The picture!
伙计  如果照片能让你好过点的话
Dude, if it makes you feel any better,
我照了很多河狸的相片
I got tons of pictures of those beavers, dude!
为什么这会让我好过
Why would that make me feel better?!
我们快离开这里  伙计们
Let's get out of here, dudes!
好了  机会来了
All right, this is it!
镜头碎了  苏斯  拍张照片
Cracked lens?! Zeus, get a photo!
你在干嘛
What are you doing?!
我们还剩一部  别担心  伙计  接住
I still got one left. Don't worry, dude. Here.
快快快快
Go go go go go!
哎  该死的
Grr! Gaa! Mollycoddling...
你能给我们多讲几个笑话吗  爷爷
Can you please tell me more funny stories, pop-pop?
为了我的钓鱼伙伴们  我什么都愿意做  哈哈哈
Anything for my fishin' buddies! Ho ho ho ho!
爷爷  我刚刚意识到  我爱你
Pop-pop, I just weawized that... I wuv you.
噢  不是吧  我呸  我呸
Aw, come on! Boo! Boo!
喂  伙计  你有什么意见
Hey, there! What's the big idea?
或许是因为没有人爱他  爷爷
Maybe has no one who wuvs him, pop-pop.
才怪  那个  我  我
Yeah, well, I-I...
苏斯  河狸啊
Zeus! Beavers!
我们还是河狸
噢  河狸
Ohh! Beavers...
-夹头术  -好  好  好
- Headlock! - Dead! Dead! Dead!
是鱼  他们来报仇了
The fishes?! They seek revenge!
快游啊  孩子们  快游
Swim, boys, swim!!!
啊  小心
Aaah! Look out!
轻点  轻点
Easy, easy...
我的玻璃
My glass!
我们要去哪里
Where do I go?!
呃  呃  去瀑布那里
Um... uh... go to the falls!
-我想那后面应该有个洞穴  -应该吗
- I think there might be a cave behind there! - "Might" Be?!
它被困住了
It's stuck!
哈哈  耶
Ha ha! Yeah!
什么  它被困住了
Wait. It's stuck?
-笨蛋  -哈哈哈
- Boop. - Ha ha ha!
你拍到好照片了吗
Did you get a good one?
全是好照片
They're all good ones!
-哇哈  -仓鼠球
- Whoo-hoo! - Hamster ball!
搞什么
What the...?
怎么了
What's wrong?
小心点  伙计
Careful, dude!
我没事  等我一下
I've got this! Hold on!
伙计们  过来看这个
Hey, guys! Come check this out!
风箱下面运转
Work them bellows in the... huh?!
啊  波兰班卓
Aw, Banjo Polish!
什么  是你
Wha... you?
这是你做的
You made this?
为  为什么
Wha... why?
那个  我
Well, I...
我  呃
I, uh...
我就是想引人注意
I just wanted attention!
我还是不明白
I still don't understand.
是这样的  首先我发明了
Well, first I just hootenannied up
生物力学脑波生成器
a bio-mechanical brain wave generator,
然后我学会了如何用胡子操纵变速杆
and then I learned to operate a stick shift with my beard.
好吧  行  但是你为什么要造这东西
Okay, yeah, but why did you do it?
好吧  因为当你像我一样老时
Well, when you get to be an old fella like me,
再也没有人会留意你
nobody pays any attention to you anymore.
我儿子几个月都不去看我
My own son hasn't visited me in months!
所以我猜靠这十五吨重的水底机器人
So I figured maybe I'd catch his fancy
也许能引起他的注意
with a 15-ton aquatic robot.
回想起来  这事情也挺勉强
In retrospect, it seems a bit contrived.
你们就是无法理解我们这些老人家为了跟家人一起
You just don't know the lengths us old-timers go through
愿意作出多大的牺牲
for a little quality time with our family.
伙计
Dude.
我猜真正的湖怪是你们两个  哈哈
I guess the real lake monster is you two. Heh heh.
抱歉  这话就是突然蹦进我的脑袋
Sorry, it just, like, boom, just popped into my head here.
那个  你跟你儿子谈过你的感受吗
So... Did you ever talk to your son about how you felt?
没有  我必须不停地改造机器人
No, sir, I got to work straight on the robot.
我一生中制造了很多机器人
I made lots of robots in my day.
例如我妻子离开我的时候
Like when my wife left me
我制造了一个嗜血翼龙机器人
and I created a homicidal pterodactyl-tron,
还有当我的朋友厄尼不来参加我的退休派对时
or when my pal Ernie didn't come to my retirement party
我制造了一个八十吨重的耻辱机器人
and I constructed an 80-ton shame-bot
把整个市区都炸开花了
that exploded the entire downtown area!
哈  好了  是时候回去弄我的死亡射线了
Aha... well, time to get back to work on my death ray!
你们有螺丝刀吗
Any you kids got a screwdriver?
好吧  拍照比赛到此为止了
Well, so much for the photo contest.
我们还剩一卷胶片
We still have one roll of film left.
你想拿它做什么
What do you want to do with it?
喂  这里
Hey! Over here!
搞什么  孩子们
What the... kids?
我以为你们跟苏斯玩转瓶游戏去了
I thought you two were off playin' spin the bottle with Zeus.
那个  我们花了一整天去找传说中的恐龙
Well, we spent all day trying to find a legendary dinosaur.
但是我们意识到我们只想跟一只恐龙玩
But we realized the only dinosaur we want to hang out with
他就在这里
is right here.
收起你们的同情心
Save your sympathy!
没有你们我也过得很开心
I been having a great time without ya...
结交朋友  跟我的影子说话
makin' friends, talkin' to my reflection...
我还跟湖警吵架了
I had a run-in with the lake police!
我现在必须戴上这个脚踝追踪器  但也蛮有趣的
Guess I gotta wear this ankle bracelet now, so that'll be fun.
所以我想船上容不下我们三个了
So I guess there isn't room in that boat for three more?
你们两个笨蛋看过我闭眼串勾吗
You knuckleheads ever seen me thread a hook with my eyes closed?
-五美刀赌你做不到  -放马过来
- Five bucks says you can't do it. - You're on!
加注五美刀赌你闭眼做不到
Five more bucks says you can't do it with your eyes closed
同时我还要声嘶力竭地唱歌
plus me singing at the top of my lungs!
这赌注我喜欢
I like those odds!
-哇啊  你的衬衫怎么了  -说来话长啊  伙计
- Whoa! What happened to your shirt? - Long story, dude.
好了  大家站在一起  说茄子
All right. Everybody get together, say "Fishing."
-茄子  -茄子
- Fishing! - Fishing!
伙计  照到我了吗
Dude, am I in the frame?
那是什么
What was that?
-谁想听个笑话  -我不想
- Who wants to hear a joke? - Not me.
哈哈  好  你就想听  开始啦
Huh huh! Yeah, you do! Here it goes.
为什么鹈鹕被赶出餐厅
Why did the pelican get kicked out the restaurant?
我不想知道
I don't care.
因为他欠下一大笔账单
Because he had a very big bill!
（注：bill也有鸟嘴的意思，“因为他的嘴很大”）
烂笑话  烂鹈鹕笑话
Bad joke. Bad pelican joke.